Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- General Secretary / Associate General Secretary Files, Series III
  - Park Sang Jung, 1981-1990
    - General
      - Conference of European Churches papers, correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - Meeting and travel reports, 1983-1990 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - South Asian Church Leaders' Consultation, 1986 October-November (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - WCC / CCA Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - General correspondence, 1981 September-December (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - General correspondence, 1982 January-April (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - General correspondence, 1982 May-December (Box 113, Folder 7)
      - General correspondence, 1983 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - General correspondence, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      - General correspondence, 1985 January-June (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - General correspondence, 1985 July-December (Box 113, Folder 11)
      - General correspondence, 1986 January-June (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - General correspondence, 1986 July-December (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - General correspondence, 1987 January-April (Box 113, Folder 14)
      - General correspondence, 1987 May-August (Box 113, Folder 15)
      - General correspondence, 1987 September-December (Box 113, Folder 16)
      - General correspondence, 1988 January-June (Box 113, Folder 17)
      - General correspondence, 1988 July-December (Box 113, Folder 18)
      - General correspondence, 1989 January-April (Box 113, Folder 19)
      - General correspondence, 1989 May-August (Box 113, Folder 20)
      - General correspondence, 1989 September-December (Box 113, Folder 21)
      - General correspondence, 1990 January-March (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - General correspondence, 1990 April-August (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - International Affairs Desk, 1982-1983 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - Meeting invitations and travel, 1982-1983 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Meeting invitations and travel, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Meeting invitations and travel, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Visitors, 1986-1987 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - WCC / CCA Conference, 1984 March-September (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - WCC / CCA Conference, 1984 October-December (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - WCC / CCA Conference, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Youth Department, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence by Country
      - Australia, 1985-1990 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - Bangladesh, 1983-1990 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      - Burma, 1987-1990 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      - Canada, 1987-1990 May (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - Germany, 1988-1990 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - Hong Kong, 1985-1989 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - India, 1985-1990 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      - Japan - Korean Churches, 1981-1990 (Box 114, Folder 19)
      - Korea, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 20)
      - Korea, 1988-1990 (Box 114, Folder 21)
      - New Zealand, Correspondence and reports, 1986-1987 (Box 114, Folder 22)
      - United Kingdom, 1986-1990 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Preman Niles, 1983-1985
    - Correspondence, General, 1982-1983 April (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, General, 1983 May-June (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General, 1983 July-December (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General, 1984 January-June (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, 1984 July-December (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Papers and sermons, no date (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - A. George Ninan, 1984-1990
    - Correspondence, Asian Health Institute Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Asian Rural Institute, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, General, 1985 November-1986 May (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, General, 1986-June-December (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, 1987 January-May (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, 1987 May-December (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1988 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1989 January-June (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, General, 1989 July-December (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, General, 1990 January-March (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, General, 1990 April-October (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jehudas Athval, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Partners in Justice Concerns - India, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Personal, 1985-1987 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Programs, 1987-1990 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Urban Rural Mission, 1984-1986 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Urban Rural Mission, 1988-1990 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Urban Rural Mission (includes reports), 1987 January-June (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Urban Rural Mission (includes reports), 1987 June-December (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, World Council of Churches, Office for Resource Sharing, 1987-1990 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Papers and Talks given, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Staff meeting incl. "Proposal for the Asian Ecumenical Center", 1986-1987 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Statements and reports from other organizations, 1986-1987 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - John Samuel, 1990-1995
    - CCA Restructuring, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - CCA review of constitution, 1992-1995 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Asia Sunday Liturgy, 1991-1995 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Australian Council of Churches, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Dedication of CCA Asian Ecumenical Center in Hong Kong (includes program), 1993 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, General, 1988-1990 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, General, 1990 March-September (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, General, 1990 October (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, General, 1990 November-December (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, General, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, General, 1992-1995 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Presbyterian Church (USA), 1993-1995 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, World Council of Churches (1 of 2), 1991 April-1994 October (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, World Council of Churches (2 of 2), 1991 April-1994 October (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, World Student Christian Federation, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Program Committee, Events and Activities, 1994 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Toshitsugu Arai, 1991-1995
    - Correspondence
      - Asia Sunday, 1994-1996 (Box 119, Folder 16)
      - Acisca, 1991-1992 (Box 119, Folder 17)
      - Acisca, 1993-1994 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - CCA Hymnal, 1994-1996 (Box 119, Folder 19)
      - CCA Library and Archives, 1994-1995 (Box 119, Folder 20)
      - Christian History in Asia Book, 1993-1994 (Box 119, Folder 21)
      - Congress of Asian Theologians, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 22)
      - General, 1991-1996 (Box 119, Folder 23)
      - Internal Communications, 1991-1995 (Box 119, Folder 24)
      - Surendra Lawrence, CCA-UNESCAP Consultant, 1993-1997 (Box 119, Folder 25)
      - Sadau Watanabe Exhibit, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 26)
      - Travel, 1991-1996 (Box 119, Folder 27)
      - World Council of Churches, 1991-1992 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - World Council of Churches, 1993-1994 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - World Council of Churches, 1995-1996 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence by Country
      - Australia, 1991-1996 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - Bangladesh, 1991-1996 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      - Canada, 1991-1996 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      - Denmark Partners, 1988-1993 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      - Germany Partners, 1991-1993 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - Germany Partners, 1994-1996 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      - Hong Kong, 1991-1996 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      - India, 1991-1996 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      - Indonesia, 1987, 1991-1994 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      - Indionesia - Churches, 1991-1996 (Box 120, Folder 13)
      - Japan, 1990 December-1993 September (Box 120, Folder 14)
      - Japan, 1993 October-1995 December (Box 120, Folder 15)
      - Japan - National Christian Council, 1995-1996 (Box 120, Folder 16)
      - Korea, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Malaysia, 1992-1995 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Myanmar, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - Netherlands, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - New Zealand, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - Norway / Sweden Partners, 1988-1995 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - Pakistan, 1991-1995 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - Philippines, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Singapore, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Sri Lanka, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - Switzerland, 1991-1994, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - Taiwan, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 12)
      - Thailand, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - United Kingdom Partners, 1991-1994 (Box 121, Folder 14)
      - United States Partners, 1991-1994, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 15)
      - United States - NCC, 1991-1994 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Programme
      - Asian Missionary Support Program, 1991-1996 (Box 121, Folder 17)
      - Christian Conference of Asia Papers, 1991-1994 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - Communications, 1991-1994 (Box 121, Folder 18)
      - Communications, 1995 (Box 121, Folder 19)
      - Communications, 1996 (Box 121, Folder 20)
      - Development Service, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Development Service, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Education Desk, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Education Desk, Asian Ecumenical Course, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Finance Committee Papers, 1994-1995 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - General Committee Meeting Materials, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - Indo-China Programme Correspondence and Papers, 1991-1993 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Indo-China Programme Correspondence and Papers, 1994-1995 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - International Affairs, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - International Affairs Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Migrant Workers, Refugees, and Internally Displayed Communities in Asia, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - Migrant Workers, Refugees, and Internally Displayed Communities in Asia, Reports and Papers, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Migrant Workers, Refugees, and Internally Displayed Communities in Asia, Reports and Papers, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - Mission and Evangelism, 1991-1994 (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - Mission and Evangelism, 1995-1996 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - National Council of Churches USA Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - Personnel file, no date (Box 179, Folder 21)
      - Personnel: Job applications (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 121, Folder 20)
      - Personnel: Job applications (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 121, Folder 21)
      - Presbyterian Church of Taiwan, Korea Papers, 1990-1995 (Box 119, Folder 13)
      - Theological Concerns, 1992-1993 (Box 122, Folder 14)
      - Urban Rural Mission Financial Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 15)
      - Urban Rural Mission, Meetings and Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 16)
      - Urban Rural Mission Reports and Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 17)
      - Women's Concerns, 1991-1995 (Box 122, Folder 18)
      - World Convention of Christian Lay Centres and Movements Papers, 1992-1993 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      - World Council of Churches Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 119, Folder 15)
      - Youth Desk, 1991-1996 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Henriette T. Hutabarat, 1991-2000
    - CCA 10th General Assembly, Colombo, Minutes, June 10-14, 1995 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - CCA 11th General Assembly, Indonesia, Minutes, June 2-6, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - CCA and Ecumenical Partners Roudtable, Program, 1994 November (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Federation of Asian Bishops' Conferences (1 of 2), 1994-1998 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Federation of Asian Bishops' Conferences (2 of 2), 1994-1998 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, General, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, General, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, General, 1999-2001 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Meeting of National Councils of Churches on Globalization, 1998 April-September (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, World Council on Churches re displaced people, 1996-1999 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Worship Workshop, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Joint Program Area Committee and General Committee, Minutes, 1995-2001 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Papers and Sermons, 1992-2000 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Papers and Sermons, by others, 1995-2001 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Process Toward a New Structure of CCA, 1994-1995 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Travel reports and minutes, 1996-2000 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Feliciano V. Carino, 1996-2000
    - Correspondence, General, 1995-2004 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Joseph Widyatmadia appointment, 1999 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Toward New Thrusts and a New Structure for the CCA, 2000 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Christine Ledger, 1996-1998
    - Correspondence, Churches in New Zealand, 1996-1998 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Congress of Asian Theologies, 1996-1998 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Gender Awareness and Sensitivity Training, 1996-1998 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, General, 1995-1996 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, General, 1997 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, General, 1998 January-May (Box 117, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, General, 1998 June-December (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Human Rights Program, 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Korean Churches, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, National Council of Churches, Australia, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, National Council of Churches, Korea, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Tosh Arai - History of finances at CCA, 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Urban Rural Mission (includes reports), 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Vietnam, Laos, and Cambodia Forum, 1996-1998 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, World Student Federation, 1997-1998 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Hong Kong Christian Council, 1996-1997 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Program Coordination: Theological Concerns and Communications meeting, Kuala Lampur, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Ahn Jae Woong, 2000-2005
    - Association of Christian Institutes for Social Concern in Asia, 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Conference on Church and Society, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Congress of Asian Theologians, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Communications Consultant, 2001-2003 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, CTC Bulletin (includes articles), 2000 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, general, 1992-1998 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, general, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, general, 2000 January-November (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, general, 2000 November-2001 February (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, general, 2001 March-April (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, general, 2001 May-August (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, general, 2001, 2003-2004 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, India, 1998-1999 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Nippon Christian Academy, 1997, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Roundtable Meeting (includes minutes), 1999 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - Indochina / VLC Forum, 1999 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Kim Yong-Bock (Marrion Kim), 1999-2000 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - National Council of Churches in Korea, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Park Sung Jung, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, Personal and Professional, 1996-1997 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Presbyterian Church, Taiwan, 1999 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases and news from other organizations, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Theological Seminary, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Urban Rural Mission Program, 1999-2000 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Prawate Khidarn, 2005-2006
    - Correspondence, General, 2005-2006 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Development Service, 2000-2001 (Box 119, Folder 28)
- Program Areas / Activities, Series IV
  - Overviews / general
    - Joint Programme Committee meeting, Bangkok, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Summary reports, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Joint Programme Committee meeting, Hua Hin, Thailand, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 29-30)
    - Summary reports, 1986-1987 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Joint Programme Committee meeting, Chiang Mai, Thailand, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence re. membership on committees, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Summary reports - "CCA Life and Action", 1995 (Box 106, Folder 34)
    - Joint Programme Committees meeting, Bangkok; summary reports, "CCA Life and Action", 1996 (Box 106, Folder 35)
    - Summary reports, "CCA Life and Action", 1997 (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - Summary reports, "CCA Life and Action", 1998-1999 (Box 106, Folder 37)
    - Joint Programme Committees meeting, Bangkok, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 38)
    - Joint Programme Committees meeting, Cipayung, Indonesia, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 39)
    - Joint Programme Committees meeting, Taipei, Taiwan, 2006 (Box 106, Folder 40)
  - Asian Christian Service
    - Administrative records
      - Agreements with governments and donor bodies, 1965-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Biographical data of staff, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Book: Fragments of War: Asian Christian Service at Work in Vietnam and Laos by Jill Perkins, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Budget, 1969-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Budget and program reports, 1973-1976 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Committee of Reference and Personal Committee meeting minutes and reports, 1970 June 8-9 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Committee of Reference and Personal Committee meeting minutes and reports, 1970 June 8-9 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Committee of Reference meeting minutes and reports, 1970 December 16-17 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Committee of Reference meeting minutes and reports, 1971 October 12-14 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Committee of Reference meeting minutes and reports, 1972 November 16 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Committee of Reference meeting minutes and reports, 1973 October 26-27 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Burma curriculum pilot project, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Burma projects, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, general, 1968-1976 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence with National Council of Churches in Japan, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence with staff, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence with WCC/Donor agencies, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, general, 1980 March-1983 May (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Director's report, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Financial reports, 1967-1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - India projects, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Indochina subcommittee, 1974 June 24 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous papers and reports, 1969-1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Pakistan refugee issues, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Personnel Committee meeting minutes, 1970 June 9 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Personnel Committee meeting minutes, 1970 December 17 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Personnel Committee meeting minutes, 1971 October 12 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Personnel Committee meeting minutes, 1972 November 16 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Personnel Committee meeting minutes, 1973 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Personnel Committee meeting minutes, 1973 October 26-27 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Programme Plans format, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Programme Policy statements, 1967-1974 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - Programme reports, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Programme reports, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Quarterly reports, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Reports from CCA visits to Kampuchea, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - Staff meeting minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Stanby Emergency Service, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - A Survey of Indochinese Refugees in Asia by Yukio Miyazaki, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - Visit to Sri Lanka by Buddhist team from Laos, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - YMCA of Bangkok project among Indochinese in Thailand, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Cambodia project
      - Agreement with the Khmer Republic, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Budget and financial statements, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Cambodia News (ACS newsletter), 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Programme format, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Programme reports, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Staff reports, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - A Summary fo the Current Situation in Cambodia with Particular Emphasis on Refugee and Social Needs prepared by Martin Bloecher, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Laos project
      - Administrative papers, 1968-1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Advisory Committee meeting minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Budget, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Field Director's report, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Field Director's report, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Financial reports, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Impressions of Asian Christian Service Medical Work in Lao s by Eduardo L. Villegas, M.D., Co-Secretary EACC Committee on Medical Work, 1971 August (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Laos Evangelical Church, 1967-1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Laos Weekly Bulletin, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Lost in the Shadows: Report on the Refugee Service Programme Survey in Laos by Samuel M. Isaac, 1968 August (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous papers and reports, 1968-1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Personnel reports, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Programme Plans format, 1969-1972 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Programme Plans format, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Programme Plans format, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Programme Plans format, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Programme Plans format, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Projects, 1967-1973 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Reports, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Staff visits to Laos, 1968, 1973, 1976, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Statistical data on proposed programme, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Vietnam project
      - ACS work in Vietnam (summaries and reports), 1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Budget and financial statements, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Central Vietnam Danang Weekly Reports, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Circular letters re. Vietnam from EACC, 1963-1969 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - "The Crucified in Vietnam" Confidential notes of Kyaw Than on the EACC and Vietnam, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Documents for the World Council of Churches Paris - Vietnam Delegates, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Emergency Relief Fund, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Field reports from Colleen Dubois to Samuel Isaacs, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Field trip reports, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1965-1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Organizational matters, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)